sheetz.com 2013-05-21

# Sheetz :: Privacy Policy : Mobile App

**Effective Date:** 11.29.2005

The Sheetz name and reputation were built on a foundation of total customer focus. Therefore, this online privacy statement tells you about the information Sheetz and/or affiliates may collect through the services available on our web site, Sheetz.com (the "Site") and other consumer electronic services that we provide, how we use that information and how you can opt out of certain uses of information we may collect. By using our services and accessing our Site, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this statement, as modified from time to time by us. We reserve the right to alter this privacy statement at any time and in any way we deem necessary. If we decide to change our privacy statement, we will post a new statement on our Site and change the date at the top of the statement. Therefore, we encourage you to check the date of our privacy statement whenever you visit this Site for any updates or changes and ensure that you understand how any personal information that you provide may be used.

Information About You. We collect several types of information on our Site. We collect "Personal Information", which generally speaking is information that can be used to identify you individually, such as your name and address. We also collect "Non-personal Information", which is information about you that does not itself identify you individually. Examples of Non-personal Information include age range and gender. We also collect "Aggregate Information", which is information about use of our site, such as pages visited on our Site. The information we collect depends on what services you use on our Site. The following is a more detailed explanation of these types of information as well as when and how we collect and use it.

Personal and Non-Personal Information. Registration and Transactional Data. When you register on our Site, we may collect various kinds of Personal Information including your name, e-mail address, home address, and home phone number. We also collect and store access information related to your account including guest name and user password. When you make purchases from our Site, we may collect purchasing information such as product orders, shipping address(es), and temporary credit card information that is deleted once the transaction has completed.

Surveys. From time-to-time we may post surveys on our Site. The surveys may request demographic information (such as age range, gender, areas of interest, and familiarity with Sheetz channels, products and services), personal information (such as name, address, and contact information) and customer feedback. Participation in these requests is completely voluntary and with each request you will have the choice of whether or not to disclose information. Such survey information will be used to improve your overall experience at Sheetz.

Customer Correspondence. We may collect information that identifies you personally when you submit comments, questions or suggestions through any collection method on our Site.

Chat Rooms. Our Site may have chat rooms, discussion boards, online forums and other interactive technologies that allow individual comments and messages to be tied to a guest's name or e-mail address. Any information you post in such forums is public information and Sheetz cannot control what uses third parties may make of personal information you share in such forums.

Resumes. If you are interested in applying for a job with Sheetz, we may collect your resume and may retain it and any information contained within for a period of time as required by law. Resumes you submit for job applications will not be used for marketing purposes.

Use of Your Personal and Non-Personal Information. Except as disclosed in this statement, we do not sell or disclose information that identifies our guests personally or makes it possible for other non-affiliate parties to contact them directly without our guests' consent. We may use, sell, disclose, or otherwise dispose of Personal Information we collect in the following circumstances:

  * Internal Analysis and Promotions. We may use information about you for our own internal statistical, design, operational purposes such as to estimate our audience size; measure aggregate traffic patterns; and understand demographic, customer interest, purchasing and other trends among our guests and customers. We may also use your Personal Information for the marketing and/or promotion of our products or services. We may outsource all of these tasks to third parties on a confidential basis.

  * Co-Branded Service Offerings. We may share this information with certain businesses with whom Sheetz has formed a strategic alliance. You may be able to identify these businesses because Sheetz has authorized them to display co-branded Web pages or links to Sheetz. These strategic partners are requested to clearly state their individual privacy policies on their own web sites or promotional materials. Sheetz assumes no responsibilities for our partners' sites and/or policies.

  * Transaction Processing. We may use your Personal Information to create a convenient and easy-to-use shopping process that includes an online "shopping cart" that allows you to track selected products and proceed through purchase. Also we may share transactional information with entities as is necessary to process credit card payments or other purchasing or delivery systems.

  * Third-Party Offers. We may arrange to have marketing and promotional information of other companies sent to you that we think might be of interest to you.

  * Legal Requirement. We may disclose personal information:

    1. to conform with the law, respond to claims or comply with legal process served on Sheetz (e.g., a lawful subpoena, warrant or court order);

    2. to enforce or apply our policies or agreements (including to initiate, render, bill, and collect for amounts owed to us);

    3. to protect and defend our or our user's rights or property, the Site, our employees, guests or the public, including fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful use of, our Site or the Sheetz Card; or

    4. if we reasonably believe that an emergency involving immediate danger of death or serious physical injury to any person requires disclosure of communications or justifies disclosure of records without delay.

Aggregate Information. We collect Aggregate Information about you and your use of our Site whenever you visit us online. For instance, we may collect various forms of "click stream" information such as entry and exit points for our Site (i.e., referring URL's or domains), site traffic statistics, page views, impressions, and operating system and browser type. In addition, when users request pages on our Site, our servers automatically log their IP addresses. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web.

We may also use third-party software that tracks traffic directed to Sheetz.com from affiliate Web sites and the purchases that result from this traffic. This information is aggregated and is not tied to an individual purchase.

This Aggregate Information generally will not personally identify you or be correlated to you individually for external purposes. We may collect, compile, store, publish, promote, report, sell, or otherwise disclose or use any and all Aggregate Information, provided that, such information does not personally identify you. When we share such information with other companies, it is not traceable to any particular user, and will not be used to contact you. If we do correlate any Aggregate Information to you, such information will be treated like any other Personal Information under this statement.

Cookies. We may make use of "cookies" on our Site. Cookies are small text files that are stored on a user's computer by a Web server based on the permissions set in a user's browser software. A cookie itself is not designed or intended to read any information from a user's computer (other than the contents of the cookie); rather, it is an identifier used by the Web site that originally placed it on your hard drive. The actual contents of the cookie information can be retrieved by the same server to identify the computer and subsequently to customize, monitor, or regulate the use of a site based on information stored on the host server. Therefore, cookies only identify the user's computer to the Web site which may correlate other information, including personally identifying information, with the cookie.

We use cookies to allow us to automate access and data entry functions of our Site such as to correlate online ordering information for purchases you may make while at the Site (if any), tailor the Site to your preferences or interests, or customize promotions or marketing. In addition, cookies allow us to track use of the Site to determine those areas which are useful or popular and those that are not thereby enabling us to improve and update the Site effectively.

You may adjust your Web browsers to either alert you of the use of cookies or refuse to accept cookies entirely. For Internet Explorer or AOL users, you can click on the "Start" button and then select Control Panel, Internet Options and the Security tab. If you click on the "Custom" button, you will be able to see the cookie options. For Netscape users, in the browser, select File, Preferences and then Advanced to view the cookie options. Be aware that if you elect not to accept cookies, the Site may not function properly or permit access.

Use of Web Beacons. We may use Web beacons on our site or other sites and may permit third parties to place them on our site to monitor the effectiveness of advertising or for other legitimate purposes. A Web beacon is a small, graphic image on a Web page, Web-based document or in another electronic document (i.e. email message) that is designed to allow the site owner or a third party to monitor who is visiting a site. Web beacons are often invisible to the user because they are typically very small (only 1-by-1 pixel) and the same color as the background of the Web page, document or e-mail message. Web beacons are represented as HTML IMG tags in the Web page; users can click on "view profiles" of the web page to see whether the page is using a web beacon.

Web beacons collect the IP address of the computer that the Web beacon is sent to, the URL of the page the Web beacon comes from and the time it was viewed. Web beacons can also be linked to personal information. For example, advertising networks use Web beacons to add information to a personal profile of what sites a person is visiting and to determine what banner ads to display based on the profile. Another use of Web beacons is to provide an independent accounting of how many people have visited a particular Web site. Web beacons are also used to gather statistics about Web browser usage at different places on the Internet.

Information Security. We limit access to personal information about you to those employees and agents who need to know the information to provide products and services to you. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with established regulations to protect personal information and we regularly review our security standards and procedures to protect against unauthorized access to personal information.

We make an effort to ensure, but cannot guarantee, that all designated affiliates or partners agree to maintain the confidentiality, security and integrity of the personal information they obtain through data acquisition on behalf of Sheetz and agree to the same level of privacy safeguards that Sheetz itself provides to its users.

Third-Party Links. The Site may contain links to third-party sites, applications, or services that we feel may be of use to our customers. Such areas have established their own respective policies and practices regarding privacy and data collection. Sheetz, Inc. is not responsible for these third-party sites, applications, or services. We recommend consulting their published policies if you have specific concerns or questions.

Children Under 13. The Site is intended for a general audience over the age of 13. Being such, Sheetz does not knowingly collect, store or aggregate Personal and/or Non-personal information from children under the age of 13.

Opting-Out of Promotional Materials. As noted above, we may use your e-mail address and other contact information provided to us through the Site or other programs to send you promotional materials from us or third parties. If you do not want to receive such promotional information, you can change your privacy preference and remove yourself from our e-mail list at any time by sending a message to sheetzweb@sheetz.com requesting removal from the list. Please be aware that such a request does not generate an automatic response. Therefore, it can take up to 1 week for the removal to be complete. During which time, you may continue receiving materials.

Notwithstanding any preference that you select, we may contact you from time to time to provide services that you have requested or for customer service matters, such as responding to service-related inquiries, updating our policies, or notifying you of changes to existing services.

If you have any questions about our privacy statement or our use of your Personal Information you can contact us by using any of the methods below:

**Mail:** Sheetz, Inc.  
5700 Sixth Ave.  
Altoona, PA 16602
